I never knew that liking someone would be this painful.
I like you.
Me too...
Tsuwabuki-kun... I like you.
The truth is, life has gotten complicated since that day.
Good morning.
G-Good morning.
Aha ha, what happened after that?
They're at it so early in the morning?
What a difficult couple.
Jeez, making us work so hard.
Hey you two, how long has it been now?
Both of them are red like cherries.
If it has gone this far, then maybe...
Yes, exactly.
To think that she is Karin-sama's daughter...
Miss, you sure are full of enthusiasm.
You don't have to work so hard, Miss.
As you are an excellent Stellar Spinear, Miss.
Ehhh?! You two haven't even been on a date?
Sumomo-chan, you don't want to have a date?
Of course she wants to!
You want to, right?
Uoooh! So irritating!
Sumomo-chan, it's time to use this!
My cell phone?
W-When did she take that...
Why don't you invite him instead, Sumomo-chan?
Me invite him?
Miss...
Dinner is served.
Miss, the sun has already set.
How about dinner? Maybe taking it in the dining room would be better...
Miss, that's bad for your health!
I wonder if Tsuwabuki-kun is busy.
He hasn't replied yet.
Oh crap, I haven't checked my cell phone today.
Well, there is still time before Sunday.
I wonder if you have to hold hands during dates.
Tsuwabuki-kun's hand must be really big.
After holding hands, next will be...
Next will be getting closer...
Stare into Tsuwabuki-kun's eyes while trying not to be nervous.
And then...
S-Sumomo?
See you later, Sumomo.
Good night.
Yuki-chan!
I can do it if it's Yuki-chan.
Good night.
Safe landing.
It's from Sumomo.
"Let's meet at Hoshinomori Park this coming Sunday at ten."
I see, so that's what it is.
The next mail is...
It's the same mail...
Akihime must be feeling nervous too.
T-Tsuwabuki-kun!
I'm sorry.
I got lost on the way...
F-First time here?
No, but I still got lost...
I see.
Errr...
Good morning!
Shall we go?
This is not good... I need to say something.
What should I talk about?
Ah, that's right!
A-Akihime...
Uh, err... Akihime?
Ah, look, a swan boat!
Oh no!
Are you alright?
Thank you for the help.
Ah, you're bleeding!
H-Here.
Thanks.
Guess I'll use it later.
Wah, it's so pretty.
Over there too!
Pretty...
It's the Bell of Hope!
Huh?
When the bell rings while a couple is together...
Umm...
the couple's future will be connected.
T-Things like that are kind of embarrassing or...
How should I say this... umm...
I guess you're right.
Oh it's from Fukamichi-san.
Did you two kiss?
L-L-Like I would!
You went on a date, but didn't do it?
Sumomo-chan, that was your first date right?
Do you kiss on your first date?
Do you?
W-Why are you asking me?!
That's because Nobuko-san has a lot of experience.
W-Well, that's...
Catch!
You! You did only that?
Listen to me! Hey!
Shut up!
A man should do this and that, all the good things!
What are you doing?!
Ahh... I give up...
Looks like we got bombarded with questions all day long.
Looks like it.
Lately, this place has become the most calming place.
It has sprouted now! Wow!
The seed we planted last time, right here.
Ah!
Right?
Yeah.
It really is.
First time with this kind of feeling.
Yuki-chan!
Sumomo!
Somehow, it's different than usual.
What do you mean?
I don't know but it feels like something good is going to happen.
Let's go, Yuki-chan!
That must be it, Yuki-chan.
Yes.
I've been waiting for you, Prima Plam.
Aspalas-san...
It's just Aspalas.
I've given up trying to correct you on that.
Prima Plam, tonight will be the time to put each of our Stellar Spinear's pride on the line for a serious match!
Aspalas-san... if that is what you wish for...
Do you see that?
That will be the star drop that we will compete to capture.
This star drop's movement is on another level compared with the others before.
Yes.
A high level star drop appeared, just perfect for the match today.
Paris Aqua Hominis!
She's walking on the water!
Arthur! Are the preparations ready?
Yes, Miss!
Hear that? Let's begin.
What should we do, Sumomo?
Watch me, Yuki-chan.
I'll do my best.
Sumomo.
It'll be alright.
W-What speed it has... alright.
Ruuche Ruvi Avis!
Puruvi Radius!
Ah, so close!
So strong...
But...!
She is using Rimu Comiti Aqua, just as expected.
I'll see if you can catch it.
I see! It's alright!
It looks like it's moving fast, but underwater it's moving much slower.
And thanks to the Recipe, you can move underwater too.
Sumomo, if you try hard enough, we can catch it if it's underwater.
I'm certain.
I'll do my best!
Puruvu Radi!
Yes!
I-It disappeared!
What was that just now?
That's the first time I've seen a star drop disappear like that.
Where is the star drop?
I can't do it!
Even if you catch it in your Ladle, it will just disappear.
Looks like its speed decreases when it tries to move out of the water.
Can you target it?
I'll try.
Sumomo!
You!
Paradivu Mei!
I guess we can only wait till it comes underwater again.
Maybe I should have tried flying a little bit further just now.
Flying further?
Note: "Kyan" in this case is an onomatopoeia similar to "swish" or "woosh" in English.
We'll try to fly further, "kyan" like that.
Sumomo?
I feel like I'm filling with energy.
Yuki-chan, I think I can do that Recipe Aspalas-san uses too.
Which one?
Just watch, Yuki-chan!
Paradivu Mei
Yay, yay!
I got wings, wings!
Yuki-chan, I'm flying!
Y-Yeah.
Sumomo, do you feel scared?
I'm alright, I'm not scared at all.
Wait!
Puruvu Radi!
Yes!
You did it, Sumomo!
She's flying without using the Ladle...
That's the fourth one, right, Sumomo?
Yes.
Get a hold of yourself, Miss!
Ah, so close!
Aspalas-san... that is...?
A star drop!
I see. So there were two of them.
It was moving around so fast so it looked like it was only one.
But...
Yuki-chan, that one is much faster.
Yeah, even though we can fly, that thing is...
But we need to do something, or...
Rimu Forna Mei. A very powerful spell, but making a mistake in using it will be... dangerous?!
W-What should we do, Sumomo?
That girl, suddenly learning new flying magic without practicing...
And on top of that a type of flying magic using shining wings instead of the Ladle.
I will not give this one to you!
Puruvi Radiu-
W-What is that?
Rimu Forna Mei!
This Recipe... It can't be!
You must be kidding! This is...
This is so mysterious right, Yuki-chan.
The star drop is moving much slower now.
Sumomo!
Puruvu Radi!
Yes!
That's great, Sumomo!
This will make it five!
T-This can't be...
Right now, I feel like I can do anything!
I feel really really excited, Yuki-chan.
Yeah!
That night was the best thing happening for both me and Sumomo.
That's why we never imagined anything really sad occurring after that.
A man keeps a secret and keeps on living...
Keisuke's ten-yen!
Don't say that!
Flora-chan's three sizes!
Hey!
Yayoi's happening...
Ehhh?!
Haru has one too.
Looks like Sumomo is going to know about it?
What are you going to do, Haru?